chattotext.com 2011-11-04

# ChatToText : Privacy Policy

We collect your personal information because it helps us deliver a superior level of customer service. It enables us to give you convenient access to our products and services and focus on categories of greatest interest to you. In addition, your personal information helps us keep you posted on the latest product announcements, software updates, special offers, and events that you might like to hear about.

## What information we collect and how we may use it

There are a number of situations in which your personal information may help us give you better products. For example:

  * We may ask for your personal information when you’re discussing a service issue on the phone with an associate, downloading a software update, registering for a seminar, participating in an online survey, registering your products, or purchasing a product. 
  * When you interact with Chat To Text, we may collect personal information relevant to the situation, such as your name, mailing address, phone number, email address, and contact preferences; your credit card information and information about the  Chat To Text services you use.
  * We also collect information for market research purposes — such as your occupation and age — to gain a better understanding of our customers and thus provide more valuable service. 
  * We collect information regarding customer activities on our websites, ChatToText.com. This helps us to determine how best to provide useful information to customers and to understand which parts of our websites, products, and Internet services are of most interest to them. 
  * We may use personal information to provide products that you have requested as well as for auditing, research, and analysis to improve Chat To Text’s products. 

## Who Has Access to It

Only people within Chat To Text who need to access your personal information can access it. 

## How We Share It

We do not sell or provide your personal information to any third parties.

We might share your personal information under the following circumstances:  

  * We have your consent.
  * We are required to share customer information by law, to protect the interests of the company or in the discharge of public duty.
  * We need to share your personal information with a business partner in order to provide a service you have requested. Our business partner's use of your information is restricted to the delivery of the service you have requested. 

## How You Change or Remove It

You have access to your personal information that we retain. We try to keep your personal information accurate and up to date. If you'd like to change or remove your personal information, please log into your account.

## Changes to this Statement

We may amend this privacy and security statement from time to time. If we make any substantial changes in the way we use your personal information, we will notify you by posting a prominent announcement.

## Security

We use current security measures to safeguard your personal information.

  * All the personal information you provide us is stored in a secure computing environment protected by secure firewalls to prevent   
unauthorized access.
  * We control access so that only people who need to access the information can. All staff of Chat To Text are required to adhere to a security agreement.
  * When you use secure areas of the site, we use Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) protocol with 128-bit encryption. This means that all the information sent between your computer and our secure computer environment is encrypted or scrambled so that no one can read it in transit. You can read it and we can read it-no one else. There are two cues to show you that you are using a secure area. First, the Web site address (or URL) appears as https:// (instead of just http://)-the "s" is for "secure." Second, a lock or key indicator appears in the status bar of your Web browser.
  * Secure areas of the site have a time-out feature. If you leave your secure session inactive for some time, it times-out to prevent   
unauthorized access. 

## Credit Cards

We do accept credit card payments for registrations. If someone uses your credit card to make an unauthorized purchase, check with the institution that issued your card to find out what the exact liability is.

## Email

If you send us an email, we may save it if we think we'll need it to communicate with you. We never sell or share email addresses. Remember, email is not a secure way to send personal information because it is not encrypted. Please don't send any personal information to us using email; use our secure forms instead.

## Cookies

Our Web site stores information in a small text file, called a cookie, on your computer. We use what is called a "persistent cookie," which is stored as a file on your computer and remains there when you close your Web browser. The cookie can only be read by the Web site that created it when you visit that site again.

## Our Use of Cookies

Chat To Text stores a unique number (not any personal information) in the cookie that we place on your computer. We use this cookie to determine if you have visited the site before, and to ensure you are only prompted once to fill in certain forms such as our account login information. The information we store in the cookie does not include data such as your name, company, email address, telephone number, state/province, country or the industry you work in.

Note: If you do not allow cookies to be saved on your computer, functionality of the site might be limited.

## Security Concerns

Once the cookie is saved on your computer, our Web site is the only site that can access and read the information that you provide. Chat To Text will not provide this information to any third parties or use it for sending unsolicited email.
